# **JONGGU JAKE BAEK**

## Front-end Web Developer

Phone: 519-330-8892 | Email: jakejonggubaek@gmail.com

## LINKS

LinkedIn: https://ca.linkedin.com/in/jake-jonggu-baek-0b153110b

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/jakejonggubaek">https://github.com/jakejonggubaek</a> Portfolio: <a href="https://www.jakeisbaek.com">https://www.jakeisbaek.com</a>

#### SKILLS

	CSS3 SAS						
NodeJS	Firebase	RES	STful APIs	Java		Responsiv	e UI
MySQL	Accessibil	ity	Team Pla	yer	Co	mmunica	tion

#### PROFILE

I am a web developer with strong responsive web design skills with other front end background knowledge to build dry, clean, and accessible applications. My passion for problem solving, an eagerness to learn and to adapt new technologies are strengthened by my previous experiences in web development & consulting roles. I am looking forward to applying my results-driven work style along with my collaboration and supportive attitude to your team.

#### RECENT PROJECTS

## Popsipoll (link)

HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, React, Firebase

 A responsive React project that provides create / share / vote polls & poll results with dark / light mode and preview poll functions.

#### Jake's Travel Survey <u>(link)</u>

HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, React, Firebase

 A responsive React project that provides travel preference survey so that travel agency can collect data of clients' travel preference.

#### Donno what to cook (link)

HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, RESTful API

 A responsive web application that provides random recipe based on what users have in their fridge.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Juno College of Technology

Web Development Immersive Bootcamp, 2021

### **Juno College of Technology**

JavaScript Course, 2020

#### **Hanyang University**

Urban Engineering B.Sc 2007 - 2013

## RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

#### Samsung SDS

Junior Web Developer, 2013 - 2015

- Managed main page, sign in, log in/out systems using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java, SQL in a cross functional team.
- Improved client's (Samsung Fire & Marine Insurance) web application successfully without any issue, and maintained the system by proactively monitoring live logs to ensure quality.
- Experienced many projects through collaborating with different companies in fast-paced environment - applied new security tools, enhanced ally, and launched first mobile application.

## OTHER EXPERIENCE

#### **Flight Centre Canada**

Travel Consultant, 2018 - 2020

- Achieved 1st tier sales goal with excellent customer service and efficient work habits.
- Contributed to the team's success to achieve the best team sales - providing support, committing to team goals.

\*References available upon request.